in this tutorial we'll be going over how
在本教程中，我们将介绍如何
you can Arch text in inkscape to create
您可以在Inkscape中拱形文本以创建
this classic athletic t-shirt design
这款经典的运动T恤设计
and if you just want to know how to arch
如果你只想知道如何拱门
text then you could skip to that part of
文本，然后您可以跳到
the lesson using the chapters in the
这一课使用
play bar below
下面的播放栏
if you do want to recreate this design
如果您确实要重新创建此设计
just make sure to download and install
只需确保下载并安装
this font that I'll have Linked In the
我将在
description of the video
视频描述
so I'll come over here into a new
所以我会来到这里，进入一个新的
document and get started the first thing
记录并开始做第一件事
we want to do is add some text so I'm
我们要做的是添加一些文本，这样我就
going to grab my text tool and I'm going
去拿我的文本工具，然后我去
to click on the canvas and I'm going to
点击画布，我要
type inkscape
类型Inkscape
and then I'm going to click again to
然后我要再次点击
create another text item and I'm going
再创建一个文本项目，我就去
to write the EST date which is 2003.
写美国东部夏令时的日期是2003年。
and then I'll come down here and make
然后我会到这里来做
one more text item that has the tagline
另一个带有标语的文本项目
which is draw freely
它是自由绘制的
and once you do that let's go back to
一旦你做到这一点，让我们回到
the select tool let's select all three
选择工具让我们选择所有这三个
text items and change their font so I'll
文本项并更改其字体，因此我将
come up here to text and I will select
到这里来发短信，我会选择
text and font
文本和字体
and from this menu we're looking for the
从这份菜单中，我们要寻找
varsity team font as it's called so let
校队字体，就像它所说的那样
me locate that highlight it and then
我找到高亮显示的位置，然后
click apply
单击应用
and now I'm just going to resize my text
现在我要调整我的文本大小
items
物品
accordingly so I'm going to make this
因此，我要做这个
one a little bigger I'll keep this one a
大一点的，我要保留这一件。
little smaller and I'll make this one
再小一点，我就做这个
the biggest ad the biggest of them all
最大的广告，最大的广告
now make sure to hold your control key
现在，确保按住Ctrl键
while you're scaling to ensure that you
当您扩展以确保您
preserve the aspect ratio
保留纵横比
and now I'm going to create a rounded
现在我要创建一个圆角的
rectangle to place behind this text here
此处放置在此文本后面的矩形
so let me grab my rectangle tool I'm
所以让我拿起我的矩形工具
going to click and drag over the object
要在对象上单击并拖动
to create the rectangle
创建矩形的步骤
and I'm going to use this little round
我要用这个小子弹
handle up here in the top right corner
把手放在右上角
to round the corners of this rectangle
要使此矩形的角变圆
rectangle ever so slightly
长方形曾经如此微妙
and then I will grab my selection tool
然后我会拿起我的选择工具
and place this beneath the text so I'll
把这个放在文字下面，这样我就
click on this button over here that says
点击这里的按钮，上面写着
lower selection one step
将选择降低一步
now I'm just going to size this up
现在我要做的就是估量一下
according to the text there
根据那里的课文
and now I'm going to select both and I'm
现在我要两个都选了，我
going to align them so let me open up
我要把它们排成一排，让我敞开心扉
the Align and distribute menu by going
通过转到对齐和分布菜单
to object and selecting align and
到对象并选择对齐和
distribute
分配
and I'm going to choose relative 2 and
我会选择亲戚2和
I'm going to align it vertically and
我要把它垂直对齐
horizontally
水平地
and with the items still selected let's
在项目仍被选中的情况下，让我们
go to path and select difference and
转到路径并选择Difference和
what that's going to do is subtract the
这将会做的是减去
text from the rectangle and now this
矩形中的文本，现在是这个
rectangle has empty space in it in the
矩形中有空白区域。
shape of those letters so that any
这些字母的形状，以便任何
backdrop that you place it on top of
你把它放在上面的背景
will show through where those letters
会显示出这些字母的位置
are
是
so let me zoom out I'm going to make all
所以让我把镜头放大，我要把所有的
of this the same color I'm going to
我想要这个颜色一样的
select everything here and choose a
选择此处的所有内容，然后选择一个
color that I'd like to work with if you
我想要的颜色，如果你
want to choose a different color other
想要选择不同的颜色吗
than what you see down here you can open
比你在这里看到的更多你可以打开
up your fill and stroke menu just double
打开你的填充和笔触菜单只需翻倍
click this color stripe over here and
点击这里的这个色条，然后
it'll open up the fill and stroke menu
它将打开填充和描边菜单
and I'm going to choose my color
我要选择我的颜色
there we go and now I just want to make
我们走吧，现在我只想做
sure that everything here is aligned so
当然，这里的一切都是对齐的
I'm going to come over here to the align
我要到这里来对齐
the distribute menu and I'm going to
分发菜单，我将
align it vertically and let me make
垂直对齐，让我来做
these items a little closer together
这些物品靠得更近一些
I'm just going to move them up like that
我要把它们像那样往上移
now again to select multiple objects I
现在，再次选择多个对象
click I click on them while holding
我在按住它们的同时单击它们
shift and while I'm moving them I'm
当我移动他们的时候，我正在
holding the control key to ensure that
按住Ctrl键以确保
they are locked to the vertical axis
它们锁定在垂直轴上
there and they do not lose their
在那里，他们不会失去他们的
alignment
对齐方式
and once you've done that let's apply an
完成此操作后，让我们应用
arch to this text right here so I'm
在这里找到这篇文章，所以我
going to click on the text to select it
单击文本以将其选中
and I'm going to convert it to a path by
我要把它转换成一条路径
going to path and selecting object to
转到路径并将对象选择到
path
路径
and now I will open up the pathfx menu
现在，我将打开pathfx菜单
so let's come back up here to path and
所以让我们回到这里来PATH和
let's choose pathfx
让我们选择pathfx
from the pathfx menu I'm going to choose
我将从pathfx菜单中选择
the envelope deformation option which is
封套变形选项是
right here
就在这里
and in the settings menu I want to
在设置菜单中，我想要
disable this setting right here that
在此处禁用此设置
says enable left and right paths we only
表示仅启用左侧和右侧路径
want to enable the top and bottom for
我想要启用顶部和底部
what we're doing here so let me deselect
我们在这里做的事情，所以让我取消选择
that and then click on this button right
然后点击右边的这个按钮
here that says Top Bend path
这里显示的是顶级折弯路径
and once you do that you'll get this
一旦你这样做了，你就会得到这个
little green line at the top of the
顶部的一条绿色小线
object here and if you hover your cursor
对象在这里，如果您将光标悬停
over you can click and drag
您可以在上面单击并拖动
to bend the text up like that
把文本像那样弯曲起来
and then we'll do the same thing here
然后我们会在这里做同样的事情
we'll choose the bottom bent path and
我们将选择底部弯曲的路径，
we'll bend that text up like that
我们要把那段文字弯成那样
and just like that we have arced our
就像这样，我们已经把我们的
text so let me grab my selection tool
文本，让我拿起我的选择工具
let's move these items up a little bit
让我们把这些项目往上移一点
and I'm just going to Center this up one
我要把这个放在一个中心
more time just to make sure everything
更多的时间来确保每件事
is still aligned
仍然保持一致
and now I'm going to make this much
现在我要赚这么多钱
bigger because if you're going to print
更大是因为如果你要打印
this on a shirt you're going to want
你会想要一件衬衫上的这个
this design to be really big so let me
这个设计真的很大，所以让我
make this a lot bigger
把这件事做得更大
again holding the control key while I
再次按住Ctrl键，同时我
scale to ensure that everything remains
扩展以确保一切保持不变
proportionate and now I'm going to
相称的，现在我要
resize my document to match this
调整我的文档大小以与此匹配
selection right here so with everything
选择就在这里，所以一切都是如此
selected I'm going to press Ctrl shift
已选中，我将按Ctrl Shift
and R or if you're using Mac it would be
或者，如果您使用的是Mac，则为
command shift and R and there we go now
Command Shift和R键，现在开始
we're finished you could take this
我们吃完了，你可以拿着这个
design export it and upload it to a site
设计将其导出并上传到网站
like Teespring or spreadshirt or
就像提斯普林或散布衬衫，或者
wherever else and have your shirt
去其他任何地方，把你的衬衫
printed so I think that should do it for
打印的，所以我想这应该可以
today's tutorial that is how you can
今天的教程就是这样，你可以
Arch text to create a simple athletic
拱形文字来创建一个简单的运动
T-shirt design using inkscape if you
使用Inkscape设计T恤，如果您
found this lesson useful then consider
发现这堂课很有用，然后考虑
checking out my inkscape master class
查看我的水墨风景大师班
it's a collection of over 60 videos
它包含60多个视频
where I go over all of the tools and
我会检查所有工具，
features in inkscape and I explain what
水墨景观中的特征，我解释了什么
they are and demonstrate how they work
它们是并演示它们如何工作
kind of like how I did in this video we
有点像我在这个视频中所做的那样，
even have a private Community where you
甚至有一个私人社区，您可以在其中
can ask questions and get help from me
可以向我提出问题并寻求帮助
anytime you want and best of all there's
任何时候您想要的，最重要的是，有
no monthly membership fees you just pay
只需支付每月会员费
17 one time and you're in for Life I'll
17一次，你就会终生难忘我会
have some information about that down
有一些相关信息
below if you want to check that out as
如果您想检查一下，请在下面作为
always thanks for watching
始终感谢观看
thank you
谢谢你
foreign
外国